Viewers all over the world, God's time is the best.
This is your pass to healing,
pass to good health,
pass to breakthrough -
receive, in the name of Jesus!
I command that affliction to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Affliction in any area of your life,
loose your grip, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can hear healing.
Healing!
Healing in your bones!
Healing in your kidney!
Healing in your liver!
Healing!
In Jesus' name!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I know your spirit is agreeing with me.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, you are restored, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Glory!
Be recovered, in the name of Jesus!
I recover your business, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Today, people run out of ideas.
People are running out of ideas.
That is why we copy ourselves.
Be recovered, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
When you are recovered for the glory of God,
you cannot run out of ideas.
Be recovered, in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Unknown
RV: Mel Flowers 25/08/2018